okay
so here is uh Aon and Sammy I believe
this is session
five um here's Aaron with 135lb deadlift
Sumo deadlift now she's stronger Sumo
see how low her hips were she commented
afterwards how heavy it was it's because
her hips were so low she's trying to
squat the weight
up uh here's Sammy with 135 lb front
squats um you'll notice the girls have
their nice little socks on they beat up
their shins from deadlifting so they
both bought uh deadlifting some some
high socks for deadlifting okay now
here's
uh 145 lbs good for him for
Aaron
uh this is Sammy 135 lbs
again um I believe I she got three sets
of five with this
which is amazing considering it's her
second time ever doing front squats
maybe she got three I wasn't
coming and
uh here's Aaron
again
uh maybe I'm doing sets at three God I'm
horrible at
counting um okay Sammy front squats form
looks really good this is
155 it's going just about parallel
and then this is uh
what
65 yep so this is 165 form looks great
here uh she gets three so 165 for
actually is she going for four there wow
four oh she gets five that's
right gets five there she felt that the
next day that was a brutal set so that's
a that's a record that's 165 for5 is um
what Aaron got God that was that's more
than her Max a month
ago um Sam again 155 front squads for
three uh good form very happy with that
and then uh this is
um good a
double needs to keep the shoulders
higher form broke down there but that's
all right use the leg drop the now
here's Sammy doing deadlifts Sumo
dead
135 you can see Sammy doesn't like
keeping her legs out uh when she
deadli with suumo and she turns her head
there which is a big no no okay now now
they traded so now here's Aaron doing
front squats this is uh 75
lbs no problem good
and here's uh Sammy here this is form
very good form 135 I'm trying to work
with her form here so I told her on set
too I said keep those knees way out I'd
rather have you do and then her form's
great here so see our knees are way
further out than last set um and she's
squatting it a little better Sammy is so
hip Dum and she wants to just when she
does Sumo she just wants to do wide
stance
conventional now here's Aaron with uh 95
lb wow one more front squats you'll see
you see me trying to take use two
cameras at once there this form is
incredible so she gets 95 for three now
here's Sammy with 185 for uh I think a
triple this is so Sammy struggles off
the floor and then flies up to lock out
she's very strong with her lock out okay
she gets five reps very happy with this
form looks a little bit more natural for
her here's Aaron this is 115 pound uh
front
squat great form him you see she's
keeping those knees out does not
struggle with the valgus and here's
Sammy this is a lot better form so
here's a 225 lb so both Aaron's NE
valgus and Sammy uh used just great form
see Aaron's knees there she's keeping
them out with heavier weight so she's
getting stronger and using better form
same with Sammy on the Sumo dead she's
keeping her knees out and using her
getting her hips low and using the knees
a little bit more uh was very happy with
Aaron's form on this um and now here's a
Sammy with let's see this is uh 75 lbs
on the for close
grip
uh can't remember how many she gets
here
three
four a little bit lower on the
chest see me Str strugles with lowering
that bar to the same position each time
this still feels very foreign to
her uh here's Aaron with 75lb front
squat
um and sometimes when Aaron gets a good
groove it just flies
up uh so yeah Aaron gets five reps with
uh with
um I had to go rescue on that one she
got four
um so they're both using 75 lbs on the
on the close grip that's right I
remember this they both did three sets
with 75
lbs um I think Sammy gets three sets of
five
and Aon gets like four I don't know what
she gets on these next sets
one
two this is great for him
three
four yep she gets five so this looks
terrific Aaron's one of those people who
gets better as the sets go
on um and Sammy third set good that
looks great
two this looks great this form is
awesome and when she uses really good
form you see how fast that flies up this
just shows you how much you know good
form makes a difference so that's SI
oh Sammy gets seven on her third set oh
she gets more okay this is number
eight eight God I don't remember this
I'm getting old okay so we got nine reps
so we'll go up next week on
those um and then here's
Aaron
four five so oh goes for six
yep so she she didn't pause on that last
rep but that looked good so there's
Aaron getting six reps okay so there
they did the power lifts and now I build
glutes so after they do the power lifts
I try to get metabolic stress in the
glutes and get them getting a pump and a
burn this is uh let's see
135 okay they just did one set that's
right so this is 135 + 150 this was 285
she got for like five reps now strip off
50 lb so this is
235 she gets like eight wraps so this is
just one mechanical drop
set okay okay she got five so five with
285 5 with
235 now this is
six
okay yep so eight with
185 and then I think she gets like 10
with 135 so this just one giant
mechanical drop set so again 285 for 5
235 for 5 185 for 8 and then 135 for
whatever she gets like 10ish maybe
she'll get a eight it wasn't counting
I'm standing on her feet so they don't
slide
forward and now here's Aaron doing the
same
uh oh my God our ax balance pad there is
broken so we're having to put it in a
weird place okay so there's Aaron this
is uh
235 and she gets
five then we're going down to 185 so
Aaron started with uh sorry Sammy
started with 285 Aaron starting with
235 so uh she gets five with
235 and
then 10 with
185 and then I can't remember how many
she gets with 135 here but
uh maybe
10 she was dying here her glutes were on
fire
here yeah she think she gets 10
2 89
go okay so now I gave them back
extensions so Sammy has not done these
in a very long time these are 100 lb
back extensions I think she gets
10 Sammy hasn't done these in a while
these are one of her favorites these in
hip
thrust um these girls were sore their
hamstrings were very very
sore uh here's Aaron with a set of
military presses this is 55 lb very
impressive Cons considering she did this
right after bench press close all those
sets of close grip bench press and she
still gets five I
believe and then here's Sammy second set
this is 50 lb back
extensions and gets 20 reps here
if you notice it looks like Sammy
hyperextends a little bit but I'm not
concerned about this she her glutes get
rock hard she uses her glutes she's
never had back pain with these so form
is dependent on the lifter if she
started complaining about back pain with
these I would try to have her being more
neutral-ish but this is fine for her and
uses glutes well so and then here's
Aaron this is Aaron's first time doing
heavy back extensions this is 50 lbs for
her so she's never done these heavy
before um and again she was feeling
these uh the next day her hamstrings and
midback were sore uh I think I teach her
on the second set to use a little bit
less
um spinal extension I think she does
better this set yep see that see the
upper back does not
uh um it's subtle difference I can tell
I don't know if you guys can but uh
using glutes really well here she
struggles to use glutes while it in
range so this is a good exercise for her
and then here's Sammy with military she
hasn't done these in
ages um you can see she's a little
wobbly I think she gets five here as
well get one more one
more she's lowering in the bar a little
too low on her chest it needs to be
right there at the upper chest and then
they finish off with band seated hip
abductions for High Reps I think they
get 20 or 30 reps here
um this is one of Aaron's best glute
exercises she gets tremendous tension in
the glutes when she does these and Sam's
hit or miss on these sometimes she gets
a crazy burn when she does these and
sometimes she doesn't feel them much in
the glutes she just needs to get better
at learning the best position position
for
her that's it for session five